how's it going everyone timbers 1345
here with a very special video today as
some of you have may notice I did not
apply a video in a while for the past
few days and this is why as you can see
i got a new head of my you channel I
made it myself and it spent me hours and
days to make it it looks good so anyway
I just want to show you guys it's really
cool like I spent a lot of time on it as
you at the bottom it says the home a
Sonic Underground it's got all the major
characters Knuckles Sonia Sonic Manic
bottle be and Mindy although you can
only see many because unfortunately I
kind of miscalculated the sauce so she's
kind of hidden behind the icon right
here no I did not put two socks there
that's that's just my icon and you can
see me at the bottom ride like what on
the right side see like I'm right here
and what all my friends are right
here and also I know is I want to make
this video is because well you see my
avatar though MaSonic it seems as though
every other week some stupid asks
me 10.5 like why do you have a crappy
picture of song as your icon well I
something say to you it doesn't
look like she looks cute I drew it a
long time ago like years ago it was my
very first picture a sock I ever drilled
in Emma's pain it just looks so cute
that I just couldn't bear to get rid of
it so so that that's why I have that as
my icon but anyways dispute about my car
it's about this my youtube head of
as I was saying it looks really bitchin
I spent like five bucks on each lens
flare so I spent like 45 bucks on this
because I couldn't really find any
lens flares on google images which I
usually get a bunch of my off of so
I had to actually buy one off off you
know I this website I don't really know
what it's called but yeah so does that
as you can see I took a picture of
myself I kid I I took the pics of myself
in my bedroom and that's how I got
picture of me right there NGC I added me
in behind the ends behind the lens flare
that's how heavily edited this picture
in a lot of time and care and how went
into it I just love it as you can see
the lens flares I was supposed to be
based off of the character you know like
a rainbow for me because well I'm a sock
on character so why the not red
four Knuckles pink for Sonja blue force
on green for Manic gold for Bobby and
there's orange back there I'm I'm sorry
it sucks balls I'm meeting you stuck
back there but anyway that there's
nothing I can do do I'm sorry in
sup it still looks really cool like I'm
so proud of him it's just many I mean
who wants to see a MRI anyway I
hope you all like it it was definitely
better than my last one at least to me I
don't really know if you guys kill or
not
or if it's just pointless upon this
piece of so hope you guys enjoyed
I'd sure did next video will be up soon
have fun wat Sonic Underground because
if bitching I love you all